[{"question":"7-6=","type":"-","one":7,"two":6,"correctNum":394,"totalNum":398,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"5+5=","type":"+","one":5,"two":5,"correctNum":395,"totalNum":399,"result1":"10","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8-6=","type":"-","one":8,"two":6,"correctNum":396,"totalNum":400,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6+6=","type":"+","one":6,"two":6,"correctNum":397,"totalNum":401,"result1":"12","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"5-3=","type":"-","one":5,"two":3,"correctNum":398,"totalNum":402,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8+7=","type":"+","one":8,"two":7,"correctNum":399,"totalNum":403,"result1":"15","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6-1=","type":"-","one":6,"two":1,"correctNum":400,"totalNum":404,"result1":"5","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-1=","type":"-","one":10,"two":1,"correctNum":401,"totalNum":405,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-9=","type":"-","one":10,"two":9,"correctNum":402,"totalNum":406,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10+7=","type":"+","one":10,"two":7,"correctNum":403,"totalNum":407,"result1":"17","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6+4=","type":"+","one":6,"two":4,"correctNum":404,"totalNum":408,"result1":"10","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"3+6=","type":"+","one":3,"two":6,"correctNum":405,"totalNum":409,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-6=","type":"-","one":10,"two":6,"correctNum":406,"totalNum":410,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4+3=","type":"+","one":4,"two":3,"correctNum":407,"totalNum":411,"result1":"7","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-8=","type":"-","one":10,"two":8,"correctNum":408,"totalNum":412,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4-4=","type":"-","one":4,"two":4,"correctNum":409,"totalNum":413,"result1":"0","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8+5=","type":"+","one":8,"two":5,"correctNum":410,"totalNum":414,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10+8=","type":"+","one":10,"two":8,"correctNum":411,"totalNum":415,"result1":"18","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9+4=","type":"+","one":9,"two":4,"correctNum":412,"totalNum":416,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9+4=","type":"+","one":9,"two":4,"correctNum":412,"totalNum":416,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9+4=","type":"+","one":9,"two":4,"correctNum":412,"totalNum":416,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9+4=","type":"+","one":9,"two":4,"correctNum":412,"totalNum":416,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"7-1=","type":"-","one":7,"two":1,"correctNum":416,"totalNum":420,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"7+7=","type":"+","one":7,"two":7,"correctNum":417,"totalNum":421,"result1":"14","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6-4=","type":"-","one":6,"two":4,"correctNum":418,"totalNum":422,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-2=","type":"-","one":10,"two":2,"correctNum":419,"totalNum":423,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-9=","type":"-","one":10,"two":9,"correctNum":420,"totalNum":424,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"2-2=","type":"-","one":2,"two":2,"correctNum":421,"totalNum":425,"result1":"0","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"7-5=","type":"-","one":7,"two":5,"correctNum":422,"totalNum":426,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"5+3=","type":"+","one":5,"two":3,"correctNum":423,"totalNum":427,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-7=","type":"-","one":10,"two":7,"correctNum":424,"totalNum":428,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"2-1=","type":"-","one":2,"two":1,"correctNum":425,"totalNum":429,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10+4=","type":"+","one":10,"two":4,"correctNum":426,"totalNum":430,"result1":"14","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8+3=","type":"+","one":8,"two":3,"correctNum":427,"totalNum":431,"result1":"11","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6-4=","type":"-","one":6,"two":4,"correctNum":428,"totalNum":432,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-9=","type":"-","one":10,"two":9,"correctNum":429,"totalNum":433,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8-4=","type":"-","one":8,"two":4,"correctNum":430,"totalNum":434,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"2-1=","type":"-","one":2,"two":1,"correctNum":431,"totalNum":435,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":false},{"question":"7-3=","type":"-","one":7,"two":3,"correctNum":431,"totalNum":436,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6+8=","type":"+","one":6,"two":8,"correctNum":432,"totalNum":437,"result1":"14","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-3=","type":"-","one":10,"two":3,"correctNum":433,"totalNum":438,"result1":"7","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6-2=","type":"-","one":6,"two":2,"correctNum":434,"totalNum":439,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"5-1=","type":"-","one":5,"two":1,"correctNum":435,"totalNum":440,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6+4=","type":"+","one":6,"two":4,"correctNum":436,"totalNum":441,"result1":"10","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"2+4=","type":"+","one":2,"two":4,"correctNum":437,"totalNum":442,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8+10=","type":"+","one":8,"two":10,"correctNum":438,"totalNum":443,"result1":"18","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"5+8=","type":"+","one":5,"two":8,"correctNum":439,"totalNum":444,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"7-2=","type":"-","one":7,"two":2,"correctNum":440,"totalNum":445,"result1":"5","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"3+4=","type":"+","one":3,"two":4,"correctNum":441,"totalNum":446,"result1":"7","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"2+2=","type":"+","one":2,"two":2,"correctNum":442,"totalNum":447,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"5-4=","type":"-","one":5,"two":4,"correctNum":443,"totalNum":448,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10+1=","type":"+","one":10,"two":1,"correctNum":444,"totalNum":449,"result1":"11","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"1+8=","type":"+","one":1,"two":8,"correctNum":445,"totalNum":450,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-10=","type":"-","one":10,"two":10,"correctNum":446,"totalNum":451,"result1":"0","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8-2=","type":"-","one":8,"two":2,"correctNum":447,"totalNum":452,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6-1=","type":"-","one":6,"two":1,"correctNum":448,"totalNum":453,"result1":"5","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9+3=","type":"+","one":9,"two":3,"correctNum":449,"totalNum":454,"result1":"12","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6+3=","type":"+","one":6,"two":3,"correctNum":450,"totalNum":455,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9-7=","type":"-","one":9,"two":7,"correctNum":451,"totalNum":456,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"5-4=","type":"-","one":5,"two":4,"correctNum":452,"totalNum":457,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9+4=","type":"+","one":9,"two":4,"correctNum":453,"totalNum":458,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6-3=","type":"-","one":6,"two":3,"correctNum":454,"totalNum":459,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9-8=","type":"-","one":9,"two":8,"correctNum":455,"totalNum":460,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9-8=","type":"-","one":9,"two":8,"correctNum":456,"totalNum":461,"result1":"1","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-1=","type":"-","one":10,"two":1,"correctNum":457,"totalNum":462,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"1-1=","type":"-","one":1,"two":1,"correctNum":458,"totalNum":463,"result1":"0","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"7-1=","type":"-","one":7,"two":1,"correctNum":459,"totalNum":464,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"7-1=","type":"-","one":7,"two":1,"correctNum":460,"totalNum":465,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10+7=","type":"+","one":10,"two":7,"correctNum":461,"totalNum":466,"result1":"17","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"2+2=","type":"+","one":2,"two":2,"correctNum":462,"totalNum":467,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"7-7=","type":"-","one":7,"two":7,"correctNum":463,"totalNum":468,"result1":"0","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-4=","type":"-","one":10,"two":4,"correctNum":464,"totalNum":469,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"5+1=","type":"+","one":5,"two":1,"correctNum":465,"totalNum":470,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9-7=","type":"-","one":9,"two":7,"correctNum":466,"totalNum":471,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"1+1=","type":"+","one":1,"two":1,"correctNum":467,"totalNum":472,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6+9=","type":"+","one":6,"two":9,"correctNum":468,"totalNum":473,"result1":"15","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4-1=","type":"-","one":4,"two":1,"correctNum":469,"totalNum":474,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9-4=","type":"-","one":9,"two":4,"correctNum":470,"totalNum":475,"result1":"5","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4+5=","type":"+","one":4,"two":5,"correctNum":471,"totalNum":476,"result1":"9","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6-2=","type":"-","one":6,"two":2,"correctNum":472,"totalNum":477,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9-3=","type":"-","one":9,"two":3,"correctNum":473,"totalNum":478,"result1":"6","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8+10=","type":"+","one":8,"two":10,"correctNum":474,"totalNum":479,"result1":"18","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"3+10=","type":"+","one":3,"two":10,"correctNum":475,"totalNum":480,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9+8=","type":"+","one":9,"two":8,"correctNum":476,"totalNum":481,"result1":"17","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9-5=","type":"-","one":9,"two":5,"correctNum":477,"totalNum":482,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10+3=","type":"+","one":10,"two":3,"correctNum":478,"totalNum":483,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4+3=","type":"+","one":4,"two":3,"correctNum":479,"totalNum":484,"result1":"7","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"9-5=","type":"-","one":9,"two":5,"correctNum":480,"totalNum":485,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4-1=","type":"-","one":4,"two":1,"correctNum":481,"totalNum":486,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-6=","type":"-","one":10,"two":6,"correctNum":482,"totalNum":487,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-7=","type":"-","one":10,"two":7,"correctNum":483,"totalNum":488,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"1+3=","type":"+","one":1,"two":3,"correctNum":484,"totalNum":489,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"8-8=","type":"-","one":8,"two":8,"correctNum":485,"totalNum":490,"result1":"0","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"7+4=","type":"+","one":7,"two":4,"correctNum":486,"totalNum":491,"result1":"11","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"2+6=","type":"+","one":2,"two":6,"correctNum":487,"totalNum":492,"result1":"8","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4-1=","type":"-","one":4,"two":1,"correctNum":488,"totalNum":493,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10+5=","type":"+","one":10,"two":5,"correctNum":489,"totalNum":494,"result1":"15","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4+9=","type":"+","one":4,"two":9,"correctNum":490,"totalNum":495,"result1":"13","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"6-2=","type":"-","one":6,"two":2,"correctNum":491,"totalNum":496,"result1":"4","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10-8=","type":"-","one":10,"two":8,"correctNum":492,"totalNum":497,"result1":"2","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"10+5=","type":"+","one":10,"two":5,"correctNum":493,"totalNum":498,"result1":"15","result2":"","correct":true},{"question":"4-1=","type":"-","one":4,"two":1,"correctNum":494,"totalNum":499,"result1":"3","result2":"","correct":true}]